[Last Episode] Oh, man! This is hilarious!
Oh, my stomach hurts.
I laughed so hard my stomach hurts.
I shouldn't have come back.
I laughed so much that I'm thirsty. I need some water.
Choi Yun announced his plans to get married.
What a selfish guy.
If things don't work out with him,
she's going to be a widow.
Why doesn't he put himself in her shoes for once?
Mother and son are so much alike
in their selfish ways.
Looks like it runs in the family.
I signed the publishing agreement.
The book will go on sale in a few days.
It'll turn the world upside-down.
Just wait a couple of days.
I'll treat you to a meal then.
Just like someone thrown away like garbage ought to,
I should have lived like garbage,
then disappear quietly, like garbage.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. But would you happen to know
where building 16-1 is?
Is this it?
Excuse me. Anyone home?
Muhyeok!
It's me. It's me, Jiyeong.
Don't you recognize me?
Muhyeok!
I worried every day that you might have already died.
I broke up with Jason.
I told Jason that I could never trade stuff with money,
even though it's as much as Australia.
I made a mistake.
Let's go, Muhyeok.
I've been asking around.
There's a famous doctor in Germany who Jason knows.
I told him about your condition,
and it's advised that you give surgery a go.
He said he'd find a way to keep you alive.
Let's give it a try.
Let's do all we can. Let's try everything, Muhyeok.
[Cha Muhyeok]
The only ones available are in the afternoon?
Fine, we'll take that flight.
Mine and Cha Muhyeok. Danny Anderson.
Who's she?
Someone you know?
When did you get here?
Go home. It's cold.
Go.
Hey, Yun.
Where are you?
Outside Muhyeok's house.
Why did you go there?
I had something to say to him.
I had something to say to Muhyeok.
Did you get to see him?
Yes, I did.
Eunchae.
All right.
Say what you need to say to him,
and I'll see you later.
Okay.
Send the reporters off.
Yes, ma'am.
What on earth were you thinking?
Who on earth makes a wedding announcement like that?
How will I ever face Eunchae's family again?
Don't you think you should've at least
given us a heads up?
Mom, you're the one who taught me this.
What?
If anyone throws a punch,
to return the favor with twice the fury.
That being weak isn't pitiful, it's bad.
What? Why on earth would you bring that up now?
That jerk who made me this way...
I want to stab him in the chest.
You what? I didn't hear.
What did you just say?
I'm saying you taught me wrong.
Yeah. That's not right.
That wasn't the right thing to do.
I should've just suffered alone.
It's all your fault, Mom. You didn't raise me right.
Yun, how can you say that to your mom?
You taught me the wrong life lessons.
Yun!
You said I should never let what I hold dear be taken.
To never give in to anyone.
Why did you teach me that?
Yun!
To avoid losing you...
To avoid losing Eunchae...
Do you know what I'm doing?
Son!
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Muhyeok.
I was wrong.
I should be punished.
Forgive me.
I'll never leave you ever again.
No matter what happens, let's never part, Muhyeok.
From now on, we'll be together till death do us part.
Let's never part again, okay?
Muhyeok!
Yes, Yun.
Where are you?
I'm at Muhyeok's house.
You're still not done talking?
No, we haven't finished talking.
I have something to say and he has something to say.
No. We're not done yet.
All right.
Are you still at Muhyeok's place?
Yeah.
Okay, I got it.
I'm coming back tomorrow.
And the day after that, and the day after that,
and all the days after...
I'll look at you till I get sick of you.
Until I stop wanting to see you,
until I get sick of you,
I will continue coming.
I won't let you order me around,
asking me to come or go as your heart desires.
To come and go as Yun asks.
To come and go as you ask.
I'm not a leaf to be blown to and fro
based on your desires.
I, too, have my own desires,
things I wish to possess,
and things I want to accomplish.
I even have things I try so hard to hold back
but end up unable to.
Do you know that?
I too am a human being who has feelings like you two!
You didn't know that, did you?
I, too, am human like the two of you!
I love you.
I love you, Mister.
I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you.
I love you. I love you, Mister.
I love you, Mister.
I love you.
I shouldn't have come back.
Just like someone thrown away like garbage ought to,
I should have lived like garbage,
then disappear quietly, like garbage.
I won't come back.
Ever.
I won't ever come back to Eunchae.
Please, take Eunchae.
You have to forget about him. You silly girl.
You made a wedding announcement.
I know, right?
Oh, my. She feels like she's on fire.
Minchae, bring some fever medicine.
Choi Yun.
Eunchae left.
She went home.
I didn't come for Eunchae. I came to see you.
Come to think of it,
you and I never had a drink together.
Since when were you such a caring guy?
I've always been kind!
If you hadn't provoked me, I'd have always been kind.
If you hadn't provoked me,
I'd have never known the love I had for Eunchae
for my entire life.
Eunchae and you.
You and Eunchae.
I would have never tried to break up you two,
who love each other to death,
and cause you all this pain.
You fell into your own trap.
Did you know that?
I know.
Pretend it's soju and drink it.
Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
What if something happens?
Pot calling the kettle black, huh?
Don't you have something to say to me?
After all, I took Eunchae and stabbed you in the back.
Don't want to say something to me?
Nothing to say, really.
I do have a few punches I wanted to dole out.
Go ahead.
If I hit you, you'd die.
Well, didn't you always want to kill me anyway?
Should we die together?
Let's die together!
We can die together and see what happens to Mom.
Let's die together.
It'd be a lot better than the revenge you plotted.
Mom.
Me and Muhyeok are going to die.
Your precious son, Yun.
And the son you tossed out like garbage,
Muhyeok, are dying together.
The Muhyeok that you abandoned
because you had no other choice...
And the Yun who you adopted,
unable to fill that void Muhyeok left,
are dying together.
What did you just say?
My mom adopted me.
I'm not her biological son.
I was adopted.
The only difference is that
you were sent overseas,
whereas I was fortunate enough to be adopted here.
There must have been a reason.
After all, she's the kind of person
who'd give up her life for me,
who isn't even really her own child.
That's just the kind of person she is.
There must have been a reason.
For a person like my mom to abandon her own children...
There must have been an unavoidable reason.
I was so scared that I'd lose her to you,
so I never told her you were back.
I used to be a good guy.
But you made me this way.
I wanted to punish you.
But because my heart was beating too fast, I didn't.
If I'd continued, I would have died earlier than you.
So I couldn't do it.
I'll go and tell her.
No matter what,
our mother
will welcome you with open arms.
Yun.
Wake up! Yun!
[Intensive Care Unit]
Yun... Yun...
- You can't go in right now.
- What?
Out of my way!
I said you can't go in now.
Who do you think you are?
I'm going to see my son! Move!
Get out of my way! Move!
Why can't I go in?
Yun. Yun...
After all, she's the kind of person
who'd give up her life for me,
who isn't even really her own child.
That's just the kind of person she is.
Why did you abandon me?
What were the unavoidable circumstances
that made you abandon me?
You even raised a great son who wasn't your own.
So why did you abandon your own kid?
It wasn't just one. It was two.
Why did you ditch me?
What was it that made you abandon me? Why?
Your dad was a married man with a family.
It was me who threw you away.
You and your sister.
Babies who hadn't yet opened their eyes.
It was I who threw you away.
Compared to the suffering you'd have had to endure
as the children of a single mother
and how you would ruin your mother's life...
And compared to how unhappy you would have lived,
I believed that was for the best for you two
and the best for your mother.
She doesn't even know she had twins.
She doesn't know anything.
We told her that you died during childbirth.
I told her that I personally spread
your ashes over a river.
I told her that.
I felt I should tell her the truth several times.
But I didn't have the courage.
I'd rather suffer alone than
to see Audrey suffer like that.
Say that again. What did you just say?
She suffered so much because of your father.
I couldn't see her go through anything like that again.
I'd rather have died than
to watch her go through that again.
Then what about my life?
Did you ever think of the lives of
me and my sister even once?
Because of you, I hated my own mother!
Despised my own mother!
That's how I spent the last days of my life!
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Did you just say you were sorry?
For the rest of my life. I'll repent for my sins.
I'll gladly accept any kind of punishment I receive.
Yes, be punished.
You must be punished.
[Song Eunchae]
[Text from Eunchae: "I love you. I love you."]
I love you. I love you.
Yun.
Just this once...
Just this once, can't I be happily in love?
I'll do whatever it takes to save my Yun.
I've lived long enough. It's fine.
I'm fine with dying,
but if my Yun were to die,
I won't be able to live, either.
Doctor, if my Yun dies, I'll die, too.
My mom adopted me.
I was adopted.
I was scared that you'd take my place.
I used to be a good guy.
But you made me this way.
Open the door!
Minju!
Open the door! Please!
Open the door!
Let's meet in the next life.
You and I
weren't meant to be this time around.
Mr. Cha. Will you take me home?
I can't get ahold of Eunchae's dad
and I have to get Yun some things.
Can you give me a ride?
I...
Mr. Cha, if I did anything wrong, please forgive me.
Even if it was unforgivable.
Take pity on an old woman like me and forgive me.
I feel like I'm being punished.
I committed the sins,
yet it's my children who are being punished.
Just because they had a bad mom,
it feels like they're being punished.
Will you give me something to eat?
What?
I'm hungry. Will you give me something to eat?
Food?
We don't have anything. Go out and grab something.
Cook for me.
Do you think I'd be in the mood to cook right now?
Please.
Please. Cook me something.
Do you want an egg in it?
You can put it in. Or not.
I left my son in the ICU.
It's hot.
Do you have to do this to me, Mr. Cha?
What are you doing? Didn't you say you were hungry?
Are you praying?
Thank you.
It's really hard to like you, you know that?
Yun, I'm sorry to have left you. What am I doing here?
There's some rice left over.
Do you want me to give you some?
Mom.
In my next life, I have to be born
as your son once again.
Then I will definitely be a kind-hearted son
who you'll be proud of.
I love you, Mom.
Are you done already?
What's wrong?
It was delicious.
I love you, Mom.
There wasn't a moment that passed
that I didn't love you.
Mom.
Thank you for bringing me into this world.
What's this? He said he was hungry
but barely ate any.
He's so hard to like.
It's really difficult to like him.
What's wrong with me?
Really, what's wrong with me?
Oh! What's that?
Someone sent it special delivery.
[Take this monee and dont releese the book
- Cha Muhyeok]
What does it say?
It asks me to take the money
and not to publish the book.
[Yun Seo-kyeong Bank Book]
Oh! That's my name!
Yun Seo-kyeong. That's my name, right?
Right. It's your name.
It seems that Muhyeok set up
accounts for Galchi and you.
It's for you and Galchi.
It'll last the two of you a lifetime.
I'm gonna publish the book.
I'm going to become rich by publishing the book.
Uncle.
What's wrong? Galchi, why are you crying?
Mom, I think Uncle left.
His clothes and shoes are all gone.
It's like he left us and fled.
Uncle.
What do we do?
It's time to board the plane. Why isn't he here yet?
[Intensive Care Unit]
[Mister Pervert]
Blockhead.
Mister.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
What's so great about me that you'd
come all the way here from Australia?
Okay. Let's date.
Someone said that the saddest people in the world are
the ones without fond memories.
I could live all my life
with just one beautiful memory...
I love you.
I love you, Mister.
I love you. I love you!
I love you! I love you!
I love you!
I'll meet my poor mother one day.
I'll buy her some pretty clothes,
some BBQ meat,
and a beautiful house.
Mom, I'll go there and let you live in luxury.
Just wait five years!
Muhyeok! Son!
My beautiful boy.
My precious son.
I love you.
I love you, son.
[One year later]
He's become much healthier.
He is alive today because
he got his brother's heart, huh?
Why didn't you publish the book?
Because I felt shame.
I'd feel ashamed if I ever saw Muhyeok ever again.
What feud do you have with Audrey?
My little sister's husband got snatched away by Audrey.
He returned to her three years later.
But by then, she was so heartbroken
that she fell ill and died soon thereafter.
He's a pretty good singer.
Audrey is lucky to have such great sons,
don't you think?
[Choi Yun's Comeback Performance]
[Ms. Song Eunchae]
This one's better, don't you think?
It certainly is hard to find
a coordinator as good as Eunchae.
I'll bring the shoes.
Did Eunchae call?
I'm sure she'll come since it's my concert.
That girl...
Must be nice to go on a vacation all on her own.
Where did she go, anyway?
[Ms. Song Eunchae]
Where'd you go?
If you had come any later...
Hey!
Mister!
Hey, dude!
Hey, mophead!
Hey!
Mister!
Hey, dude!
Hey, mophead!
Are you Japanese? I'm Japanese too.
Are you Chinese? I live in Chinatown, too.
You Korean?
You're Korean?
I'm saved!
Saved!
Mom...
Wait! I have a husband! I'm married!
With children!
Just go to sleep! Unless you want to die.
[Here lies Cha Muhyeok]
[News Editing Department]
[The body of a Korean woman was found beside
a grave in the outskirts of Melbourne, Australia...]
He had been terribly lonely even while alive.
So I couldn't allow him to be lonely
afterwards as well.
Just for once in my life. Just this once...
I'll be selfish.
And live for my own sake.
I'll accept the punishment for my sins.
Song Eunchae.